Rang Mahal is inside the Red Fort in Old Delhi.
It was part of the harem inside the fort.
It is also called Imtiyaz Mahal.
During the rule of Shah Jahan, it was known as the Palace of Distinction.
It is one of the major attractions inside the Red Fort.
The inside was once richly painted and decorated.
Some rooms are called Shish Mahal.
They are called that because tiny pieces of mirror cover their ceilings.
The Nahr-i-Bihisht flowed through the centre of the marble palace.
The Nahr-i-Bihisht flowed into a marble basin carved into the floor.
After the British occupied the fort in 1857, Rang Mahal was used briefly as a mess hall.